[
    {
        "categoria": "Números",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "El Número 5",
        "incorrecta1": "Una Mano",
        "incorrecta2": "Adiós",
        "incorrecta3": "Pare",
        "imagen": "./images/5.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Números",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "El Número 9",
        "incorrecta1": "El Número 0",
        "incorrecta2": "El Número 8",
        "incorrecta3": "pozo",
        "imagen": "./images/9.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Números",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "El Número 6",
        "incorrecta1": "Por favor",
        "incorrecta2": "Adiós",
        "incorrecta3": "Disculpa",
        "imagen": "./images/6.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Números",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "El Número 8",
        "incorrecta1": "Febrero",
        "incorrecta2": "Domingo",
        "incorrecta3": "Julio",
        "imagen": "./images/8.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Meses",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Febrero",
        "incorrecta1": "Mayo",
        "incorrecta2": "Adiós",
        "incorrecta3": "Disculpa",
        "imagen": "./images/febrero.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Meses",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Abril",
        "incorrecta1": "Enero",
        "incorrecta2": "Adiós",
        "incorrecta3": "Octubre",
        "imagen": "./images/abril.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Meses",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Septiembre",
        "incorrecta1": "Octubre",
        "incorrecta2": "Noviembre",
        "incorrecta3": "Número 12",
        "imagen": "./images/septiembre.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Meses",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Noviembre",
        "incorrecta1": "Agosto",
        "incorrecta2": "Lunes",
        "incorrecta3": "Mi Nombre es",
        "imagen": "./images/noviembre.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Meses",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Diciembre",
        "incorrecta1": "Gracias",
        "incorrecta2": "Por Favor",
        "incorrecta3": "Junio",
        "imagen": "./images/diciembre.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Frases",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Bienvenidos",
        "incorrecta1": "Gracias",
        "incorrecta2": "Por Favor",
        "incorrecta3": "Diciembre",
        "imagen": "./images/bienvenidos.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Frases",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Buenas Tardes",
        "incorrecta1": "Buenos Días",
        "incorrecta2": "Buenas Noches",
        "incorrecta3": "Por Favor",
        "imagen": "./images/buenas_tardes.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Frases",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Buenas Noches",
        "incorrecta1": "Buenos Días",
        "incorrecta2": "Buenas Tardes",
        "incorrecta3": "Feliz Cumpleaños",
        "imagen": "./images/buenas_noches.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Frases",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Feliz Cumpleaños",
        "incorrecta1": "Felicidades",
        "incorrecta2": "Letra F",
        "incorrecta3": "Adiós",
        "imagen": "./images/feliz_cumple.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Frases",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Gracias",
        "incorrecta1": "Felicidades",
        "incorrecta2": "Letra G",
        "incorrecta3": "Saludos",
        "imagen": "./images/gracias.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Días",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Lunes",
        "incorrecta1": "Martes",
        "incorrecta2": "Letra G",
        "incorrecta3": "Letra O",
        "imagen": "./images/lunes.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Días",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Miércoles",
        "incorrecta1": "Jueves",
        "incorrecta2": "Domingo",
        "incorrecta3": "Saludos",
        "imagen": "./images/miercoles.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Días",
        "pregunta": "¿La siguiente seña corresponde a:?",
        "respuesta": "Sábado",
        "incorrecta1": "Felicidades",
        "incorrecta2": "Disculpas",
        "incorrecta3": "Saludos",
        "imagen": "./images/sabado.gif",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    }
    
]